This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed to Navy Headquarters to rescue his brother Ace from execution.
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard Pirates have successfully stormed Marine Ford to save Ace
and triggered an all-out war with the Navy.
Boars, no!
Now, climb up Boars' body and charge!
Waaah!
Waaaah!
What the?
D-R!
D-R инструмент!
Tension grows at the battlefield.
I think my poor heart is about to go kabloo-ing!
Can you slow us down somehow? There's gotta be something!
What good old wax works in a time like this?
Why are Luffy and the others falling from the sky?
Good question.
To figure out what happened, we'll have to go back in time.
The marine ship that Luffy and company were on
was hit hard by Whitebeard's destructive sea quake.
It feels like it's starting to pick up speed!
Hey! Behind us!
Oh hell no!
It's a tsunami!
It's huge! And it's headed our way!
This is no natural occurrence. Only one man commands such fierce a power.
Hey! Jinbei! Wake up!
Gotta do something!
Stupid tsunami!
No way in hell I'm gonna let myself lose to that dumb thing!
I gotta get to Ace and save him!
Bring in the sails!
Hold on Luffy! We're going to ride this tsunami!
Is that a good idea?
That moron's gonna get us all killed! I'm not ready to die yet!
Turn around you fool! Give me the wheel!
Hey! Stop it!
The tsunami's getting closer!
Jump into the sea!
What? How would that help?
And you call yourself pirates?
It's common sense, amateurs.
If we turn around now, the wave will strike the side of the ship and we'll capsize.
Riding it is our only option.
So there you have it!
Unless you all want to end up washed away, everyone better hold on tight!
Gotcha!
Hurry up!
Just grab something!
Hey, think! My head's too big!
It's just hitting that spider hive!
I don't want to end up with this 쓰 in space, is the only point that I'm towards parking.
It depends on that one's worth!
I know it for the disk of the ship.
Bestider!
llega forever!
Set it down!
What the heck?
The waves stopped moving.
How in the world did that happen?
Huh?
That is messed up!
I mean, at least we're not dead.
But what are we supposed to do?
Take an ice pick to this thing?
I think I know who did this as well.
Just take a look below.
The answer's clear enough.
It's the old man.
The battle's already started without us.
It's just as I thought.
He set off that sea quake as a declaration of war,
and Admiral Aokiji froze the tsunami in response.
Hey, guys, listen up!
I got an idea that'll get us down there.
We got less than three hours to work with,
so this is our best chance to save Ace from getting executed.
Uh-huh.
Go on.
Are you mad?
You want to slide all the way down this frozen wave back into the sea?
That's it.
But first we gotta wiggle the ship free so we can actually start sliding.
Need I remind you, this is a battleship.
It's not going to wiggle easily.
Did you hear that, you idiot?
If we work together, I know we can do it!
When you put it that way, it sounds pretty cool.
Oh, right!
If Captain Buggy, the next king of the pirates, thinks we can do it,
then anything's possible.
His fighting spirit is rubbing off on us!
Buggy's the best captain ever!
Yeah!
Put-a-put-a-put-a-put-a.
Attention all ships and soldiers!
The new target is T-O-T-T-Z.
Commence change in formation and make the shift to Operation 3.
Sounds like the Navy is busy giving out orders.
Advance all preparations now!
T-O-T?
What do you think that means?
Dunno.
Maybe some sort of secret code they're using.
Once all soldiers are in place,
we will move the schedule forward and execute Ace immediately.
That is all!
Colleen!
Luffy, no!
Let's move!
There's no time for arguing!
We can't bum around any longer!
Everyone, follow Strawboy's lead and help move this ship!
Let's go!
Hey, wait a minute!
No, let the roar fly!
And that is how Luffy and the others ended up falling from the sky.
So EASY
Whoa!
hate this game off
worms
bucket
Oh, boy.
Did that really happen?
A navy ship fell out of the sky like it was nothing!
Water! It's water!
I thought we were dead!
I figured we'd all be goners once the ship crashed into the ice.
Hey, why isn't it frozen here?
Look! The ship landed in the exact same spot where Jozu ripped out a chunk of ice!
Could it be a surprise attack?
No, those guys don't look like the navy.
Grab hold! Start climbing!
Ha! This ain't got nothing on the water torch and we went through an impel down!
What use are devil fruit powers if you can't even swim?
What is this place?
Oh yeah, we were stuck on that wave.
Oh yeah, we were stuck!
Oh cut!
Save me!
Ace!
Here.
Damn it! Where is he? Ace!
Get on the ship!
Guess he's not over here!
Man, where is he?
Hold on, Ace! I'm coming for you!
Out of my way!
Ace!
I'm coming for you!
He's alive!
Ace!
Ace! I'm here!
Luffy!
Ace!
Finally found you!
Luffy, no!
Ace! I'm coming! Hang on!
Hey, is that who I think it is? It's Crocodile!
And he's not the only one either. Just take a look at that line-up.
A who's who on both sides. All the big names are here.
The world can't handle this madness!
Hey, Ace! Sit tight, okay?
Cause we're gonna get you outta here!
Hey, Garth! Your family's messing things up again!
Luffy, no!
Look! Straw Hat's got some company!
It's Jinbei! And the Revolutionary Army Zivankov!
There's a ton of infamous pirates behind them too!
They must've all escaped from Impel Down somehow!
Straw Hat's causing trouble again, is he?
I'm not surprised.
Is that Straw Hat!
What is Straw Hat Luffy doing here too?
Looks like he forgot to bring his crew along with him.
Luffy! I'm so relieved to see that you're alive!
I can't believe it, Helmepo!
What is it? Not another surprise, I hope?
Straw Hat!
That's crazy! That means he must've escaped from Impel Down!
How much tougher can this guy get?
Now those are some big fish we're staring at.
Well, fancy seeing him.
That boy sure gets around, huh?
Guess that's the famous kid brother Ace was always telling us about.
A former and active warlord hand in hand!
And look!
We even have the famous rookie Straw Hat in attendance!
This is too good!
Smoker, look there! Quickly!
Eat this!
Up!
Straw Hat Luffy and Crocodile.
What are those two doing together?
So it is him.
The grandson of our very own marine hero, Garp.
And the son of the revolutionary dragon.
I'll make that boy regret the day he decided to become a pirate.
Of all things, you have the gold to allow yourself a Straw Hat Luffy.
After all we've done for you, you're a badass like this!
That's right! I choose to resign from the Seven Warlords!
Rather peculiar. All these groups uniting against us.
Time to kick free!
Prisoners. A commander of the revolutionary army.
Those gaudy looking fellows.
And Crocodile.
I highly doubt everyone here has a common goal in this battle.
They're all too different for that to make any sense.
That doesn't make any sense.
What?
Where'd Crocoboy go?
I guess the sucker chickened out and left us high and dry.
Wait! There he is!
Damn it! You're supposed to wait for me!
It's Crocodile! He's going straight for Whitebeard!
Long time no see, old man.
You never learn.
Oh!
Straw Hat knows too well what my strengths and weaknesses are.
Once you touch water, then you can't turn into sand anymore.
You know, there's only one reason I'm here.
If you want to save your brother so bad, stay out of my way.
I'm killing Whitebeard and you can't stop me.
So that old guy is Whitebeard. I thought so.
Just stay away from him!
He's Ace's friend, so I'm not gonna let him get hurt!
Well, would you look at that?
It runs in the family.
Huh?
Don't let him get close to Pops!
When you came back from East Blue missing an arm, you better believe the rumors were flying.
I was pretty curious myself.
Now I can ask you face to face, what enemy did you give that left arm to?
Don't worry. I gave it to a kid.
Hey, Squirt. That straw hat that you're wearing. It looks exactly like the one red-haired Shanks used to have on him.
Hold on. How do you and Shanks know each other?
You're right. It was his hat. He left it to me.
Can you believe it, Pops? Look! This dork is my kid brother!
You came here to rescue your big brother?
That's right.
Do you have the slightest idea who our forces are up against?
A squirt like you is gonna get slaughtered real easy!
2-inal
Shut up! You don't know? You don't even know me.
I know what you're up to yeah you want to be the king huh first you gotta go
through me
what a cheeky little punk don't come crying to me for help if you get a few boo-boos spoiled
brat yeah right I'm not all old like you I'm gonna be the one to rescue Ace he's competing
how cute I would assume this is all punishable by death right Sengoku definitely Luffy my family
you just said tight Ace I'm coming for you you're not gonna die today
Luffy leaps into the fray battling against familiar faces and new foes alike he races
towards the scaffold like a whirlwind of destruction and as his brother begs for
him to turn back Luffy shares some powerful words of his own on the next one piece even
if it means death Luffy versus the Navy the battle starts I'm gonna be king of the pirates